(Bernadette:)Excuse me, I have to pee.
(Bernadette:)Or is that
implausible, as well?!
(Howard:)It's nice to have another
couple to hang with, isn't it?
(Penny(to the shoes):)All right, guys,
you have to go back.
(Penny(to the shoes):)I can't afford you.
(Penny(to the shoes):)No, don't send
us away; we love you.
I love you, too,
but you cost more than my rent.
But, Penny,
you look so good in us.
Damn it, the shoes are right.
(Amy:)Good golly, Penny,
your whimsy is boundless.
(Amy:)What do you got for me,
wildebeest?
(Bernadette(in Raj's bathroom):)I think they're on to me.
(Bernadette(in Raj's bathroom):)The story's starting
to fall apart.
(Amy:)Calm down.
Everything's going to be okay.
(Amy:)We may have
to kill her.
(Amy:)Bernadette, I'm putting
you on speakerphone.
(Amy:)Where are you now?
(Bernadette:)In the bathroom.
(Amy:)Oh, look at this, another one of
our classic bathroom gabfests.